[Music]
back in 2012 when we started the
industry there was no life insurance to
speak of here in Cambodia and I would
like to take this opportunity of saying
how proud we are we helped introduce
this great industry to Cambodia with the
help of the ministry of economic and
finance we've been able to run seminars
around the country over a hundred
thousand people have attended and have
been able to understand the vital role
that life insurance plays not only in
their future for the future of the
country
Becky reciting mere a pro athlete with
me reduce my study the silver cap alarm
in the black onyx conversation bethere
IBM integration logically that man
choice had decided modern handles around
four million caravans Anglin a structure
in which comes in which language
conversation with you discovered
commanding to enact a traumatic time
people really come they simply keep play
the people do by mental planted pet
northern mom the lowest gear sex happens
maternal offices review mediator :
Rodimus coordinator pro Samsung tryin
rockin rockin Fontanella Pro a huge
events module life Cambodia solo here
chrome frontier after I delivered the
30th last own property become to mera
Providence with Lagrange's cambogia no
man can reach Guardian on to neurology
for our campuses and filter action candy
cotton ear a provocative earth Samrat
velocities Wrangler Mukunda
conversations unity
Samuel the appendix random the top in
the Fram chair menses lorida young
Martin Thomas good a lot Mohammed hi
Bianca's via copy young fella from
channel 9
Lane baram Etrigan wall key possession
cool parent and I'm inanimate are
multiple Union people die most
well-known parasite clapping guitar
client knows get mouthy ancient China
play Laura Montes de pantalons I don't
know me I'm not jungle Pierre Thomas
quite an enjoyed all my kinetic Roman
new line I didn't some crappy peasant le
i'll CIE control mahadji like this young
women look at just how scaramouche's
gold diamonds and athletes bank of
Scottie socialization a unit
[Music]
I'd also like to thank our Planck
partners they have been fulsome in their
support and encouragement to Manulife in
Cambodia we've been able to bring our
products and solutions to many of their
customers to give them peace of mind
the partnership with such a reputable
financial institution is honorable and
important to us with this partnership we
combine the expertise with manualized
with our extensive distribution network
including our digital channels to offer
our clients the high quality life
insurance products with a protection and
long term financial stability
[Music]
the bank is very pleased to have menu
life as our insurance partner when your
life has a suite of comprehensive
insurance product that meets the needs
of our customers together may bank and
manual life has a unique formula we are
like m and M chocolate sweet colorful
and comforting together we provide
security and protection to our customers
in good times and bad times
[Music]
we are confident that our relationship
will continue to grow stronger as our
organization cooperate to bring more
financial innovation to the oblation of
Cambodia for our customer it is
comforting to know that their bank
trusts Manulife it is one thing to know
a brand and Manulife is a great brand
but it is another to entrust the future
of their family to a company so we tell
our customer you can trust among your
life it's actually really complimentary
to the solutions that were and the aims
of our our clients because they want to
protect and grow their wealth and the
solutions that Manulife offers enables
them to plan for important financial
objectives so the partnership allows us
to work with our clients and also to
contribute to the prosperity of the
country
this is a relationship that wing values
and it gives high regard to from wings
perspective as we offer breadth and
depth of payment system we also offer
improvements in innovation and
technology and that's why the
relationship has been very very good
very strong and we continue to benefit
from each other I also like to thank our
staff I think that they are the finest
group of people that I have ever worked
with they have grown in confidence and
we believe passionately in the life
insurance industry and in this great
company
the muy guapa TOA for a terminological
union culture more that you find the
truth net to win tomorrow hire very
friendly people society you so minimum
poverty families and we hire you're
motivated to work at Catholic origin to
attend oku around the poverty meals at
all and I could pay I'm a total of our
children come to you called ogod fair
paneer aroma Gucci work near campus
coupon times what we can write that I've
decided gives like the Lord come upon
many logical untied just cooking for
about 14 weeks simple time for some of
them for science and I ban law and
academic simple all day okay that's a
budget pin and I like ingenious methods
work on a piece of mat appear Dagon
through the mountain bike remember need
a gelato publication ban total ban house
or wimpy we catch items in the bathroom
for black are a kangaroo box unit in
banchon
Muslims that have disabilities and cats
with hydrogen for rupee install the
functionality for locking the pigeon
thermal energy and driving specialist in
changeable plug that's what for
gathering the materials online which can
be found of companies about the Moto G
associate director
[Music]
I'm also very proud of the CSR work that
we have done here in Cambodia our road
safety campaign with AIP has definitely
saved lives and the differences to the
people we have donated over 4,000
helmets and run education programs to
help children understand the dangers of
road safety mechanical musical can
maintain cabe assessment whatever take a
million people back home to burn finance
of naturalizer mmm government like
Cambodia man Chuang commotion card was
even dreamt I like time kappa nothing a
diagram Julia gives them the contractor
papayas no Control Committee the year
and the water stands at home
[Music]
we're also very proud of the Angkor Wat
Hospital for children that we have
helped support over the last three years
and the Angkor Wat international half
marathon which has really been a
tremendous international event and I
thank very much the National Olympic
Committee for their support and guidance
and helping us support that program
[Music]
and Manulife our purpose is to help
people achieve the dreams and
aspirations of putting customer needs
first and providing the right advice and
solutions and given that Manulife was
the first international life insurance
company in Cambodia it is very exciting
to see the impact and growth that we've
had in the Cambodian market long-term
success in our business means putting
Cambodians first as well as facilitating
the healthy development of the Cambodian
economy and I'm proud to say that we are
equally committed to both I would like
to take this opportunity to thank all of
our customers in Cambodia for putting
their trust in us and allowing Manulife
to protect their financial future and
help them attain their financial goals
at the same time I'm very thankful for
the tremendous support from the Royal
Government of Cambodia and all of our
local business partners we are grateful
for the opportunity to work together to
help the life insurance industry prosper
and to see all of Cambodia thrive thank
you all food
[Music]
man your life and the life insurance
industry is a long-term relationship
with our customers with our staff and we
look forward to developing this great
industry into one of the finest in the
region I could
[Music]